{
    "id": "8e1a43396f1347f09dee2cf66dfab35f",
    "title": "Present Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My father …………………. for a walk in the morning. (Habitual action)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "is going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. coffee in the morning. (Habitual action)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "drinks",
                "am drinking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Flowers ..................... in the spring. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bloom",
                "blooms",
                "are blooming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds ..................... their nests in trees. (General truth)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "make",
                "are making"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The pigeon .....................… the art of nest-making.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not know",
                "do not know",
                "does not know"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Deciduous trees .....................… their leaves in the autumn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shed",
                "sheds",
                "shedding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody ...................... dishonest people. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter .....................…… in a factory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ..................... . abroad. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. best in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "am working"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}